let topics = {
    general_topic: [
        {
            question: "What causes ocean tides?",
            correctAnswer: "The pull of gravity from the Moon and the Sun",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "The pull of gravity from the Sun",
                "The pull of gravity from the Moon",
                "The Earth spin around its axis",
            ],
            hint: "Not only one cause",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the biggest animal that ever lived?",
            correctAnswer: "Blue whale",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "King Kong",
                "Tyrannosaurus rex",
                "Sperm whale",
            ],
            hint: "Fish",
        },
        {
            question: "What is culture?",
            correctAnswer: "The features of everyday life shared by a group",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "A person's individual traits",
                "Something different that one person does in their daily life",
                "Having respect and acceptance for people different than you",
            ],
            hint: "Stem from more than one person",
        },
        {
            question: "Who sets the standards that create a culture?",
            correctAnswer: "All People",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Family Elders",
                "Artists",
                "Governments",
            ],
            hint: "Something that is normal",
        },
        {
            question: "Which is not a danger to explorers searching for the lost city?",
            correctAnswer: "Rabid monkeys",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Deadly snakes",
                "Hungry jaguars",
                "Poisonous insects",
            ],
            hint: "Animal that contains non-contagious disease",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a property that leads to electromagnetic interactions between particles of matter?",
            correctAnswer: "Electric charge",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Static electricity",
                "Electric conduction",
                "Semi-conduction",
            ],
            hint: "Intake of electricity",
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the following is not an element of which color is composed?",
            correctAnswer: "Detail (definition)",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Value (hue)",
                "Intensity (saturation)",
                "Tonality (luminance)",
            ],
            hint: "HSL",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the measurement of Earth's gravity?",
            correctAnswer: "9.8 m/s2",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "8.2 m/s2",
                "6.9 m/s2",
                "3.5 m/s2",
            ],
            hint: "Can be rounded up to 10 m/s2",
        },
        {
            question: "BarmBrack, a fruitcake, is a Halloween Irish tradition. This cake contains:",
            correctAnswer: "Objects baked into the bread used as a fortune-telling game",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Special powers that will make you see ghosts",
                "Chili and different spices",
                "Meat",
            ],
            hint: "Something for prophecy",
        },
        {
            question: "Which of the following is NOT a major component of Cell Theory?",
            correctAnswer: "All organisms contain eukaryotic cells",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "All organisms are made of 1 or more cells",
                "The cell is the basic unit of life",
                "All cells come from pre-existing cells",
            ],
            hint: "Not the fundamental root of an organism",
        }
    ],
    math_topic: [
        {
            question: "Bo is buying candy by the pound. For every 10 pounds, he pays $23. What is the cost per pound?",
            correctAnswer: "$2.30",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "$0.43",
                "$1.50",
                "$23.00",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "Which statement describes a unit rate?",
            correctAnswer: "Sam is driving 40 miles per 1 hour.",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Sam ate 1 piece of pizza.",
                "Sam ate 4 cookies and 1 almond.",
                "Sam is driving 40 miles.",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "Mr. Ramsey bought 5 pounds of dog food for $10. How much did he pay per pound in dollars?",
            correctAnswer: "$2.00 per pound",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "$50.00 per pound",
                "$5.00 per pound",
                "$15.00 per pound",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "Jim used 3 hours to drive 150 miles. At that rate, how far would he drive in 8 hours?",
            correctAnswer: "400 miles",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "24 miles",
                "1200 miles",
                "50 miles",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "Steve ran 1 lap in 7 minutes. At this rate, how far would he run in 42 minutes?",
            correctAnswer: "6 laps",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "10 laps",
                "5 laps",
                "7 laps",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "There are 12 yards of fabric. Each pillow uses 2/3 yard. How many pillows can be made?",
            correctAnswer: "18 pillows",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "8 pillows",
                "12 pillows",
                "15 pillows",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "Twelve whole pizzas are eaten. Each person eats 1/4 pizza. How many people eat pizza?",
            correctAnswer: "48 people",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "16 people",
                "8 people",
                "24 people",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "The area of a rectangle is 25/42 and its width is 5/6. What is the length?",
            correctAnswer: "5/7",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "1.3/7",
                "1.2/5",
                "125/252",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "The area of the triangle is 1/8. What is the length of the base?",
            correctAnswer: "2/9",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "1/18",
                "1/9",
                "9/2",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "A 21-foot long rope is cut into 3/8-foot pieces. Which expression finds the number of pieces?",
            correctAnswer: "21 ÷ 3/8",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "21 × 3/8",
                "3/8 ÷ 21",
                "21 − 3/8",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
    ],
    calculation_topic: [
        {
            question: "1 + 1 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "2",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "3",
                "4",
                "5",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "1 x 10 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "10",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "30",
                "40",
                "50",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "11 x 12 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "132",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "69",
                "145",
                "213",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "99 - 72 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "27",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "34",
                "49",
                "52",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "3 x 2 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "6",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "9",
                "10",
                "5",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "0 / 1 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "0",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "1",
                "100",
                "10",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "99 / 3 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "33",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "66",
                "49",
                "11",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "3! = ?",
            correctAnswer: "6",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "7",
                "9",
                "10",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "9 ^ 2 = ?",
            correctAnswer: "81",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "67",
                "63",
                "72",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
        {
            question: "sin(0) = ?",
            correctAnswer: "0",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "1",
                "0.3",
                "0.6",
            ],
            hint: ""
        },
    ],
    environment_topic: [
        {
            question: "Which of the following objects can temporarily resist the force of gravity?",
            correctAnswer: "Airplane",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Train",
                "Boat",
                "Motorcycle",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Which source of electric energy is non-renewable?",
            correctAnswer: "Coal",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Solar panels",
                "Windmills",
                "Dams",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Which type of rock is formed from the cooling of lava and magma?",
            correctAnswer: "Igneous",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Mineral",
                "Sedimentary",
                "Metamorphic",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Which type of rock is made from many other rocks cementing together in layers?",
            correctAnswer: "Sedimentary",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Mineral",
                "Igneous",
                "Metamorphic",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Where does the sun find its greatest source of water to turn into vapor?",
            correctAnswer: "Oceans",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Puddles",
                "Lakes",
                "Rivers",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "If humidity needs warm air and moisture to exist, which environment would have higher humidity?",
            correctAnswer: "Rainforest",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Tundra",
                "Grasslands",
                "Desert",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Which environment has higher latitudes, moderate precipitation, and low temperatures?",
            correctAnswer: "Tundra",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Rainforest",
                "Grasslands",
                "Desert",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "If the Sun is shining in the sky over Florida at 1:00pm on Tues., where will it be in 24 hours?",
            correctAnswer: "Shining in the sky over Florida",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Shining in the sky over Africa",
                "Setting in the West in California",
                "Rising in the east over Japan",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Why does the Earth have changing seasons?",
            correctAnswer: "The Earth revolves around the Sun every 365 days",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "The Sun revolves around the Earth every 365 days",
                "The Earth's rotation every 24 hours",
                "The amount of humidity the Sun creates in the atmosphere",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "Of what is Earth's crust made?",
            correctAnswer: "Rock",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Oxygen",
                "Magma",
                "Water",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
    ],
    coding_topic: [
        {
            question: "What is a list of steps you can follow to finish a task?",
            correctAnswer: "Algorithm",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Program",
                "Bug",
                "Code",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is an error in a program that prevents the program from running as expected?",
            correctAnswer: "Bug",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Program",
                "Algorithm",
                "Code",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is finding and fixing errors in programs?",
            correctAnswer: "Debugging",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Program",
                "Code",
                "Bug",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the action of doing something over and over again?",
            correctAnswer: "Loop",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Persistence",
                "Code",
                "Program",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a sprite?",
            correctAnswer: "A 2D object on the stage that can be given commands",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "A set of commands that run in order from top to bottom",
                "Computer",
                "The area where all commands are typed",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is the stage?",
            correctAnswer: "The area where the visual output of a program is displayed",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "Finding and fixing the error or bug in a program",
                "The area where all commands are typed",
                "Python",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a comment?",
            correctAnswer: "A line that is used to provide information about the code",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "The unit of measurement on the stage",
                "A 2D object on the stage",
                "The area where all commands are typed",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a variable?",
            correctAnswer: "A name that stores a value",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "The area where all commands are typed",
                "A block of code containing commands",
                "Program",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a Pixel?",
            correctAnswer: "The unit of measurement on the stage",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "An object on the stage",
                "Code",
                "Codesters",
            ],
            hint: "",
        },
        {
            question: "What is a Binary Code?",
            correctAnswer: "Information that a computer can understand",
            wrongAnswers: [
                "The matrix trilogy",
                "A social media website",
                "Fraction",
            ],
            hint: "",
        }
    ]
};